Today, nationwide, is Mother's Day.
Regardless of whether or not you like your mother...
Regardless of whether or not your relationship with her is good...
If you're a Japanese citizen, you'll take this matter seriously.
I didn't come to this park with a solid reason.
Only purely, randomly, aimlessly...
riding on my mountain bike.
Riding and riding until I reached this park.
But for me to be the only one in the park even though it's a Sunday...
It's as if I'm the only one in the entire world, isn't it?
This may be a bit of an exaggeration,
but it feels as if I have the rights to the entire park.
Like I never need to go back home anymore.
That's how I feel right now.
Only me.
I'm all alone.
Alone again, huh?
This comes as no surprise.
That's why...
Koyomi, that's why...!
My, my. What do we have here?
I thought the carcass of some dog had been left here...
But what's this? It's Araragi-kun?
What? It was just a greeting.
It was only a joke.
Ah, i-it's nothing.
Or perhaps the innocent Araragi-kun was fascinated by my charming clothes...
and felt a moment of bliss.
Let's not worry about that pun.
I am indeed fascinated.
But you know, "fascination" is a pretty amazing word, isn't it?
Did you know...?
It's written with a "grass" radical on top of "hot water."
In my heart,
it's a level above the word "moe," which is written with a "grass" radical on top of "bright."
People are expecting it to carry onto the next generation.
Note: The Kanji read "Next World" which is a pun for "Maid"
Like "maid fascination" or "cat ears fascination."
They'll be going and saying things like that.
The impression that these clothes give off
is quite different from the ones I've seen you in before, so I was surprised.
That's all.
That's true.
That's because I chose to wear more docile clothing at that time.
Oh, is that it?
Even so, I bought this set of clothing, top and bottom, yesterday.
I must say, I'm content.
If possible, I wanted you to see it first.
That you wanted to show it to me first...
How do I put it...?
Maybe I'm beyond lucky...
I feel honored.
I didn't want to show them to you, Araragi-kun.
I wanted you to see them.
The nuance in those statements is entirely different.
By the way, Araragi-kun...
What are you doing here alone?
Well, I was just riding around a bit.
I was riding my bike randomly,
and there was a park,
so I decided to stop and rest a bit.
You?
Do you come around here often?
This area used to be my turf.
Your turf...?
You mean you used to live around here?
Yeah, you could say that.
But it has changed completely.
I'm not going to get sentimental over it,
but the place where I used to live changing is...
It feels like it just cuts off my motivation, for some reason.
Isn't that inevitable?
You're right. It is inevitable.
Hey, Araragi-kun, do you mind if I sit beside you?
Beside me?
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Sure.
I was starting to feel bad, keeping the entire bench to myself.
Is that so?
Then I shall help myself.
About what happened before...
I wanted to thank you one more time...
You don't need to thank me or anything.
You should thank Oshino instead. I think that's more than enough.
Well, I have to pay Oshino-san, so it's a bit different.
As for you, I wish to express my gratitude differently.
Well, if you are feeling grateful to me...
You should just stop now.
Otherwise it will be hard for us to get along from now on.
Get along?
Araragi-kun...
May I think of you as someone close to me?
That... Of course.
But you are the type who doesn't make many friends, right?
That was true until last year.
Then a paradigm shift occurred during spring break.
What about you?
I was the same until recently.
More specifically, until I met you.
What does she mean?
And what is this weird situation?
It feels as if she's about to confess to me.
Which means, Araragi-kun...
Regardless of what you say, I still wish to reward you for your help.
After that, we will, for the first time...
become friends of equal status.
Friends...
Hence, Araragi-kun, is there anything you want me to do for you?
I will only take one request, but it can be anything.
A-Anything?
Really, anything is acceptable.
No matter what the wish, I will grant it. However, you are limited to only one.
Be it "world domination," "immortality,"
"defeating the Saiyans headed to Earth right now"; all is acceptable.
You...
Do you possess powers that surpass those of the Eternal Dragon?!
Of course.
Such confidence.
But indeed, truthfully, I'd prefer to hear a more personal wish.
Because it's easier.
I'd assume so.
Really, anything you want.
For example, you might want me to put a "nyu" at the end of every sentence for a week.
Or perhaps you will want me to go to class without wearing panties for a week.
Maybe you'll want me to wake you up every day for a week, wearing nothing but an apron.
Or you might want me to join you on an enema diet for a week.
You have many different preferences, don't you?
You...
Do you really think that I'm at that level of maniac perversion?!
Even coming from you, isn't that way too rude?!
No... That... I'm really sorry.
I guess if you said you wanted me to do that forever, I wouldn't be able to take it...
No. Wrong. That's completely wrong!
I'm not angry over the fact that my level of perversion has been lowered.
Oh, is that so?
As a reference, I personally recommend "waking you up every day for a week, wearing nothing but an apron."
I can also make breakfast for you, if you like.
Isn't viewing that from behind romantic for a man?
You know, Senjougahara...
Even if we make that sort of arrangement, I think us just being "friends" will be impossible.
Ah, if you put it that way, you have a point.
You're right.
Then let's just say that erotic things are off-limits.
Besides, I figured that you wouldn't ever ask for anything erotic, anyway.
You have a great deal of trust in me.
Well, of course. You're a virgin.
I guess we did talk about that, didn't we?
Virgins aren't that greedy, so I'm more at ease.
Umm... Senjougahara.
You don't have any experience either, right?
What are you talking about? Of course I have experience.
I see...
Experience with orgies.
Say, even if that's true...
What do you get out of telling me the truth?
I understand. Correction:
I don't have any experience.
I'm a virgin.
Huh?
Which means the only girls who would talk to hopeless virgins like you are
at best, late-blooming virgins with mental health issues such as myself.
The conversation seems to have gone a bit astray...
But honestly, is there anything you need help with, Araragi-kun?
Something that you're just troubled about?
Troubled...?
I'm not a very good talker, so I can't say it very well,
but my intention of wanting to help you is sincere.
I see.
If I dare to tell you...
Oh, what is it?
Try telling me about it.
You'll feel better if you just talk about it. Or so they say, anyway.
Umm...
I had a fight with my little sister.
Seems like something I can't help with very well.
But for the time being, go ahead and tell me the rest of the story.
"For the time being"?
Which of your younger sisters did you have a fight with?
You have two younger sisters, after all, don't you?
Yeah. You knew that?
If I had to pick just one, it was the elder one.
But, really, it was with both of them.
Both of them, always, whatever they do, and wherever they are, stick firmly together.
They are the Tsuganoki Middle School Fire Sisters, after all.
You even know their nicknames?
Today is Mother's Day, right?
Now that you mention it, it is, isn't it?
Both of them are really close to our mother.
My mother dotes on them like they're cats.
And...
I see.
As the irresponsible eldest son,
now, on this day, today, Mother's Day, you have no place at home, is that it?
That's basically it.
I tried to sneak out of the house early in the morning, but...
Just as I'd gotten on my mountain bike, my sister caught me.
We then had a quarrel.
A quarrel?
My sister wanted me to celebrate Mother's Day together with my mother.
But, how do I put it...?
You know, I just can't.
Koyomi, that's why...!
That's why no matter how much time passes...
To sum it all up, a person like me who can't celebrate just one Mother's Day...
is angry with himself over what his four-years-younger sister said to him.
How do I put it...?
I'm angry with myself for being such a petty human being.
That's a pretty complicated problem.
It's not complicated. It's just minor.
"I'm just a really petty person," or something like that.
But even so, the more I think about having to apologize to my sister, the more I don't want to go home.
You don't want to go home, huh?
I'm afraid to say that in regard to your pettiness, there's nothing I can do, even with my abilities.
How about a little encouragement?
It's rather obvious, but in regard to your pettiness, there's nothing I can do, even with my abilities.
You must be thinking that I'm a boring person...
Troubled over such a small thing...
I can't really...
stand it.
Small.
It can also be said to be lame. The sort of lameness that comes from getting a fortune told by a fortune teller.
You can't deny that you're charming, Araragi-kun.
Charming?!
Could it be that my charm has been drawing low-luck from fortune-telling all this time?!
I was kidding.
Besides, your lameness isn't drawing low-luck from fortune-telling.
Are you trying to say that I'll only be able to draw terrible-luck?
Of course not.
That would be most incredible.
Or rather, that would be quite favorable.
Your lameness is something like...
Drawing a great-fortune, but when you read it specifically, it doesn't say that anything that good will happen.
That sort of lameness.
That really is lame.
But Araragi-kun, you look like the type to dote on your sisters.
Always quarreling.
Are they ugly sisters who'd make your eyes bleed from looking at them?
They don't make my eyes bleed!
Or did she betray your love?
Could you secretly be a siscon?
No, that's not it.
Falling in love with your sister... is just a fantasy by those who don't have sisters.
Okay, then Araragi-kun, you aren't a siscon.
You won't fall in love with your sister?
How could I?
That's right. You seem more like a sorocon.
Sorocon?
The short form of sororate marriage.
Also known as inter-marriage inclusive of all sisters.
It means marrying the older or younger sister of one's wife who passed away.
Why am I a sorocon?
In your case, Araragi-kun, you will most likely marry the younger sister instead of the older one.
Basically, you'll get your wife's younger sister...
to call you "Big Brother," and then you'll marry her afterward.
Even after getting married, you will still let her call you "Big Brother."
This is what it originally meant.
Then I definitely killed that previous wife!
Well, Araragi-kun, the sorocon...
Please call me a siscon. I beg you!
Didn't you say that you won't fall in love with your sister?
I will also not fall in love with the sister of my wife!
Then will you fall in love with a lover that is not blood-related?
Like I said...!
Huh? A lover that is not blood-related?
"You sure are petty." Such a small joke is enough to leave you speechless.
Your words are not some small joke, you know.
I was testing you just now.
Why am I being tested?
Wait, does that mean you're still not going at me at full force?!
To use my full potential, I'd have to transform.
Transform?!
Wow, I really want to see that!
You make such huge reactions, but you yourself are petty.
But regardless of how petty you are, I will never abandon you.
I will cope with you and your pettiness to the bitter end.
Your words are complicated.
That's why, besides your pettiness, are there any other things you are troubled about?
How do you plan on scolding me this time?
Your significance has increased. Incredible.
Don't praise me in such a forced way!
Is there really nothing else you wish for?
Would you like me to help you with your studies?
I have already given up on that.
It's fine as long as I'm able to graduate.
Then do you want me to help you with that?
I can live normally and graduate!
Then do you want to be normal?
Are you picking a fight with me? You are, aren't you?!
I guess I am.
Do you want a girlfriend?
What happens if I say I do?
Then you will have a girlfriend. That's all.
No, actually I don't really want a girlfriend.
Oh, is that so?
Buy me some juice next time.
That should settle it.
Is that so? That's really unselfish.
You're so noble.
That child was also here just now.
Hey, Senjougahara.
How do you read the name on the name tag of that elementary school kid's bag?
I don't see anything like that.
Oh, a normal person shouldn't be able to see it at such a distance.
Umm, the numbers "eight," "nine," and "shrine."
The "eight" and "nine" plus "shrine" write out to be "eight nine tera."
Well, that's pronounced "Hachikuji."
Hachikuji?
So her name's Hachikuji Mayoi.
She doesn't look like the type that likes small kids.
Hey, could you wait here for a second?
Yes, but where are you going?
I'm going to go talk to the elementary school student.
You shouldn't. You'll only get a scar on your heart.
How can she say these spiteful things so nonchalantly...?
Yo. What's up?
Are you lost?
Please don't speak to me. I hate you.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I'm hurt. That's all that happened.
I'm going to try again.
What exactly are you doing? Where are you going?
Can't you tell with your eyes?
Hey, you.
You're lost, aren't you?
Where are you going?
Let me take a look at that memo.
Hey.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I was ignored by an elementary school girl.
This time definitely... I'm going!
I don't really know what you want to do or what you're doing...
Ignore me!
What do you think you're doing?!
So you finally turn around.
Anyone would turn around after such a beating from behind.
Well, it looked like you were having some difficulties.
So I was wondering if I could help you.
The kind of help a person who would suddenly attack an elementary school kid's head could offer...
doesn't exist in this world!
Absolutely impossible!
I'm sorry, okay?
Um, my name is Araragi Koyomi.
Koyomi?
It sure sounds like a girl's name, doesn't it?
Girly, don't come near me.
So what's your name?
I'm Hachikuji Mayoi.
I'm called Hachikuji Mayoi.
This is an important name given to me by my mom and dad.
In any case, stop talking to me.
I hate you.
Why?
I won't harm you.
There isn't a more harmless person than me in this town.
Very well, then. I'll be less alert with you.
That will make things easier.
Then, beastly man.
Beastly man?!
Who are you calling that?!
He's yelling at me! I'm so scared!
I'm sorry for yelling at you, but "beastly man" is going just a little too far.
Anyone would have yelled.
Then, how should I address you?
Well, a normal way of addressing me is good enough.
That is Araragi-san, right?
Yeah, normal is good. Normal is the best.
I hate you, Araragi-san.
Please leave immediately!
No. As I was saying, you're lost, aren't you?
A minuscule problem like this is hardly a problem for me.
Don't be so stubborn.
I am not.
You are.
Take this!
This is the end!
Ouch!
You're so stupid.
Did you think that an elementary school student could beat a high school student?!
There was a figure of a man...
who fought an elementary school kid, threw her over his back with all his might,
and was boasting about his victory from the bottom of his heart, despite the fact that he was in high school.
Actually, that's me.
Araragi-kun.
Please allow me to explain.
Go ahead.
Well, let's just brush aside things of the past.
She seems to have lost her way.
I was thinking that I could help her.
Hmm, really?
No, I see.
I understand the circumstances.
Ah, right, Senjougahara.
If you heard the address of this area, you'd roughly know where it is, right?
Well yes, to a certain extent.
Hey, Hachikuji.
Give this girl a look at that memo.
It seems that I had a dream of being abused by an evil high school boy.
Having that happen in real life sounds impossible.
I see.
Impossible, huh?
What's wrong? Take it.
I don't feel like touching you.
It's only touching the memo.
I also don't wish to touch the things you've touched.
All right, I get it.
I will read it. Is that fine with you?
Eh...
Do you know where this place is?
I know that place.
That's good.
I don't know the exact location.
But we should be able to find it based on our senses when we get there.
Then, let's go.
Let's go, Hachikuji.
Oh, where are we going?
Like I said, we are going to the location written on the memo.
That girl knows the way. She will lead you there.
Isn't that great?
Ah, she'll lead the way...?
Are you not lost?
No, I'm lost.
I'm the lost child of a snail.
Snail?
No, I...
It's nothing.
I'm Karen.
I'm Tsukihi.
Even the kids of the kings are considered kings, right?
I've gotten that.
Reading kings seem kind of fake, don't they?
But the thing earlier seemed more like reading to me.
Oh really?
Because of corruption, they apparently become like kings.
But every once in a while, aren't the kings a bit stronger?
So nowadays reader kings are kind of in a heartbreaking state, huh?
A heartbreaking state, eh?
Quiz time.
It's that time, right?
Tsukihi-chan and I are twins, right?
We're not twins!
Which of the 12 constellations is known as the twin constellation?
Isn't it Gemini?
No, actually, Pisces is also a twin constellation.
It's true!
It's true?
Next time, Mayoi Snail Part 2.
But it may not necessarily be a twin.
It could be like us.